I have a video about how an investment savings account works
Both advantages and disadvantages.
Is it that you want to know more about an investment savings account then you can check out that video
An investment savings account is perfect
For those of you who want to start investing your money and unable to keep track of what you have bought and what you have sold
How much you have to pay in taxes and declare and stuff like that complicated
Without you open an investment savings account, you deposit money you start investing, and then solve yourself
And you get a very low tax
The only thing you should think about when investing money on
An investment savings account is that money you invest
Should stay in the investment savings account.
You should not use your ISK as
A salary account when you lock in and out money without money that you deposit into an investment savings account should stay there.
This of tax reasons
Step number 3 I usually say but start by buying a fund
Buy a free Sweden fund for example
Avanza Zero or Nordnet Index Fund Sweden
These two free funds
The better with interest on interest effect
so the money will work for you
the more wealthy you will be
Money that you invest it is thus money
that you should be able to afford to lose
money that you can afford to delay
thus to be without
in perhaps three to five years at least
Keep in mind that historical returns are
No guarantee for future returns
It means that